Jamie and Bo, you can stand up, don't be
shy.  Jamie and Bo.  Yes, here
they are.  But you're an assistant.  Let's.
They have a special website called
Knowledge Bas, and they post
about 5,000 videos there and another 5,000 that
they are currently editing, about 10,000
videos.  And it's all free.  And they
worked very hard to make all these
descriptions.  And now they
are working, ah, Bo is working on
Lamrim.  How much did you finish?  Five
five courses, right?  It's
already six.  And
she connects it with the original language.
She did all this work together with
her
14-year-old assistant Lamrim.  And you can
watch all this for 14 years for free
on the street.  Let's give a round of applause and
thanks for
that.  They always give me the same answer
.  We meet for dinner once a year
or once every 10 years.  I ask: "Guys, do you
need money?"  They say, "No, these are the
only people who tell me,
'No, we don't need money.' They say,
'No, no, we don't need it, we're
fine.' But, of course, they accept
donations. So, if you're
watching the classes on this site, I
urge you, I encourage you, please
make a donation. They're the
only one who doesn't ask me for money.
Really, really. So you should
help them. I hope you'll
help. And I... Yes, we had dinner together.